So, oh, it's hot.
Yeah, my Har Tish baby loves to help
mama. Hi my friends.
Since Ganesh Chaturthi is coming,
we're fasting.
Look at this.
My beautiful, beautiful temple
with our roses
from our rose bush outside.
We're fasting this month for the whole
month for Shravan. And we'll say prayers
for you guys as well. Today, I'm going
to be making
chana rolls, which is a very, very uh
big thing in Goa. So, we're going to be
making that today. My Har Tish baby
loves to help mama cook. So, he's over
here washing the rice for me.
We have the corn over here. We have our
blender out because we're going to start
doing
our masala mixture for the chana rolls.
Here, I make my own masala. And here's
our beans. We're going to be doing the
green whole peas.
So,
this is the roasted masala here, all the
whole spices.
Har Tish, my baby, is over here. He's
roasting the coconut, freshly grated
coconut.
This is our rice that we're going to
start boiling.
I'm making Lavish's plate. He has papad,
corn on the cob, rice, and then we have
some chana rolls right here, guys. And
this is for Har Tish, papad, pickle. He
has salad, cucumber salad, rice, and
then we got some chana rolls that I'm
going to be putting on his plate.
Okay, let's put some chana rolls on your
plate.
Yum, yum, and the yum, yum. This is Har
Tish's favorite
all the time.
You want
>> Yeah.
>> More, more, more, more?
>> Yeah, I want all of it.
>> All of it.
Boys, let's try.
What do you He's like, I don't know what
to eat first.
>> I don't know. I don't know.
>> Just take a small bite and go, "Oh, it's
hot."
>> It's really hot.
>> Just take a little bit just to show
everybody and then you can let it cool
down.
Eat.
Oh, yummy, yummy.
That's his favorite. He loves papad.
With some chutney, no?
You don't have to eat it all.
Oh my goodness, you're making a mess.
Good. Good. Is it good?
One out OF 10?
GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, BOYS, ENJOY.